Bryan Harper

www.philectrosophy.com/about bryanbharper@gmail.com | 970.274.3342

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MISSISSIPPI

BSEE IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING Graduated June 2017 | Oxford, MS College of Engineering Dean's Honor Roll (2014-2017) Major GPA: 3.81 / 4.0

MA IN ANALYTIC PHILOSOPHY

Graduated May 2014 | Oxford, MS College of Liberal Arts Chancellor's Honor Roll (All Semesters) Cum. GPA: 3.89 / 4.0

LINKS

Website:// philectrosophy.com GitHub:// brharper-clgx

SOFTWARE

LANGUAGES

C# • F#

Typescript • Javascript Haskell • Python

TECH

.Net • Entity Framework
Fable • Elmish
Angular • Hangfire
Postgres • Cockroach
Git • XUnit • NBomber
Selenium • Sauce • Jenkins
Node • NPM • PCF • GCP

BEST PRACTICES

TDD • Agile / XP Paired Programming • CICD SOLID • REST APIs FP • Automation Testing

ABOUT

Agile Software Engineer experienced with contributing to multi-team development projects. Collaborative developer, knowledgeable in programming environments ranging from new, cutting-edge microservice architecture to legacy applications in need of some clean-up. Devoted to helping teams build solutions and work together to learn and succeed.

EXPERIENCE

CORELOGIC | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

July 2017 - present | Oxford, MS

- Full stack web development on agile team dedicated to TDD and best-practices.
- Worked with business analysts, engineers, and project managers to deliver cloud-native .NET Core microservice applications.
- Rewrote legacy application with 200K+ users to meet client requirements for functionality, scalability, and performance with focus on testing and modernizing the application for future maintainability.
- Exhibited strong technical aptitude and expertise resulting in optimized performance, continuous delivery, and product innovation.
- Coordinated with other engineers to evaluate and improve software and integrate across systems.

HYPERION TECHNOLOGY GROUP | PAID INTERNSHIP

Jan 2017 - July 2017 | Tupelo, MS

• R&D for embedded systems and IoT devices from contract specifications.

TELEDYNE OPTECH | NASA/MSSGC INDUSTRY INTERNSHIP

May - August 2016 | Kiln, MS

- Independently designed and developed system tracking software; now used for inventory, version control, and maintenance.
- Hardware testing and calibration. Surface mount soldering.

NASA EPSCOR | Undergraduate Researcher

2016 - 2017 | Oxford, MS

- Research in Cognitive Radio, Channel Coding, and Spectrum Sensing.
- Paper selected for presentation at the National Conference on Undergraduate Research.

UM DEPARTMENT OF PHILOSOPHY | ADJUNCT INSTRUCTOR

Aug 2014 - May 2015 | Oxford, MS

• Lectured and guided students on the fundamentals of rationality and the application of formal and informal logic to problems in philosophy and public discourse.

AWARDS & SOCIETIES

2020			Hackathon Winner	
2019			2 nd Place - Google Hackathon	
2016	_	Present	Eta Kappa Nu	IEEE Honor Society
2015	_	Present	Pi Mu Epsilon	Mathematics Honor Society
2012	_	2014	Graduate Fellowship	For academic excellence
2012	_	2014	Graduate Tuition Scholarship	For TA work